### Способы связаться

vladimir.slepovron@gmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/wladimirsawicki-16761499 (LinkedIn) slepovron.github.io/ (Portfolio)

#### Основные навыки

JavaScript NodeJS Git

### Languages

Русский (Native or Bilingual)
English (Limited Working)
Polski (Elementary)

# Wladimir Sawicki

Frontend Developer / IT Engineer

Moscow, Russian Federation

### Общие сведения

A junior frontend developer with a long experience in system administration and IT analytics. Worked in both large companies and small businesses (including freelancing and volunteering). Ready to relocate to Poland (also considering proposals for a remote

### Опыт работы

Self employ Frontend Developer февраль 2016 - Present

Moscow

job).

I have been working as a frontend developer since the end of 2018. Creation and make changes to web pages on request. I use the following knowledge and tools:

HTML5 / CSS3 (Flexbox and Grid layout, Bootstrap4, Boilerplate, AnimateCSS)

JavaScript (ES5 / ES6 depending on the project)

Version control system: Git (Github)

Local web server: Node.JS, XAMPP (lamp), VSCode Live Server

JS compiler: Babel

Module bundler: Webpack (currently study the React.js library ecosystem)

Code editors: VSCode, Sublime Text, Atom

Operating systems: Windows, Windows Server, Linux (Mint, Parrot Security,

Ubuntu)

As a basic knowledge of the network structure, I draw on the long experience of a systems administrator and IT analyst (also including the management of the IT security infrastructure).

As additional skills I can specify:

Information security (including mobile security) and personal data protection.
 I actively participate in specialized conferences and training sessions from

manufacturers of forensic solutions, specialists in pentest and ethical hacking (Elcomsoft, Oxygen Software, Electronic Cloud, TMGroup).

- Understand the structure of blockchains and distributed ledgers (both in terms of financial interaction crypto asset, and in terms of business technologies).
- Trading and financial market analysis based on technical analysis. Work with financial assets of crypto market, exchanges, fiat gateways.

I have working and volunteering experience in foreign countries (Nepal, Vietnam, Thailand).

#### Avon

Sr. IT Infrastructure Analyst, Eastern Europe декабрь 2014 - декабрь 2015 (1 год 1 месяц) Moscow, Russian Federation

- Senior IT Infrastructure Analyst, Eastern Europe (Senior System Administrator)
- Domain forest based on Microsoft Server 2008r2 (ADDS, WSUS, DHCP, DNS, GPMC, FS, TS, FTPS, etc. support and development of the existing LAN/WAN infrastructure), equipment HP, Dell, IBM, Cisco,
- Server virtualization based on VMware VSphere,
- Backup and recovery systems: Symantec Backup Exec, Veeam,
- Monitoring systems: Nagios, IBM Tivoli,
- Websense network security solution,
- TrendMicro antivirus software,
- Video and audio conference: Polycom Telepresence, MS Lync / Skype for business, Adobe Connect,
- Avaya Aura PBX,
- CRM services: Hardware Inspector, Remedy, IBM Notes/Domino, OTRS,
- Office equipment: Xerox, HP, Konica Minolta, Kyocera.

Participation in projects and activities:

- Support of the global project on transition from Windows Server 2003 to Windows Server 2008r2 / Windows Server 2012r2 at the regional level
- Elimination of the global problem of unauthorized access to the Internet by users in a workplace with terminal access
- Development and implementation of the global policy for using of the file servers,
- Introduction of secure printing using SafeQ technology,

- Development, coordination and implementation of the correct standard transliteration of Cyrillic usernames,
- Conducting the activity for safe use of the Internet traffic created by users on remote production sites

Self employ

System administrator, IT manager. сентябрь 2013 - июнь 2014 (10 месяцев)

Vietnam, Thailand

IT freelance in a foreign country (Vietnam, Thailand).

- Search for clients (hostels, restaurants, private clients),
- Configuration and support of local networks and network equipment, backup organisation, search and elimination of the causes of failures, information security,
- Recommendations for repair and replacement of equipment.

«Oboronenergo» open joint-stock company Senior System Administrator январь 2011 - июль 2013 (2 года 7 месяцев) Москва, Россия

- Senior System Administrator (7 employees, 5 units, 18 servers, 800 users)
- Domain forest based on Microsoft Server 2008R2-2012R1 (ADDS, RODC, IIS, FTP, WSUS, Hiper-V, DHCP, DNS, GPMC, FS, TS, organization structure and replication OU), equipment HP ProLiant DL 160/360, Dell, Depo, IBM,
- Network equipment: HP, 3com, Netgear, ZyXEL, D-Link, TP-link (VLAN, WDS)
- Gateway Kerio Control 8 (NAT, PAT, VPN, Kerio-VPN, L2TP, PPPoE),
- NAS servers on the basis of Netgear, QNAP,
- Panasonic PBX: KX-TDA100, KX-TDE100, KX-TDE200, IP-PBX Asterisk (Elastix), Free-PBX,
- Video and audio conference: Panasonic Communication Assistance, MS
   Lync 2010, Skype, Google Hangouts
- Legos ACS Access control system (implementation, configuration, programming, access zone)
- CRM systems: Hardware Inspector, OTRS, 1C EDS
- The backup: Acronis Backup, Acronis True Image,
- Implementation of 1C Enterprise 8.1 (SCP and Workflow) training,
- Staff Cop Standard monitoring system,
- Office equipment: Konica Minolta, HP, Kyocera,

- Network design and putting into service,
- Interaction with counterparts
- Maintenance of applicants new IT staff (interview, hiring / firing, etc.).

I have got a reference letter written by the Company General Director and it can be provided if required

Foundation "Institute for Urban Economics" System Administrator июль 2010 - декабрь 2010 (6 месяцев) Москва, Россия

- Domain structure based on Microsoft Server (Windows Server 2003, AD, File Server, DNS, DHCP, GPO etc.) and end-user support (Windows XP / Vista / Se7en, Windows Mobile 6 / 6.1 / 6.5)
- MDaemon mail server administration,
- Remote access and user support (VNC, DameWare, Team Viewer),
- Working with established bank customers (Sberbank, Taxcom),
- Support internal telephony (Panasonic TDE 100)
- Administration of systems of corporate security, anti-virus applications, firewalls (Kerio Control, NOD32),
- Administration of OS Microsoft SQL Server 2000 2005.
- Installing and configuring the operating system Microsoft Windows XP Windows 7, office applications, Microsoft Office 2003 2010, OpenOffice,
- Working with contractors (equipment suppliers, mobile operators, service providers, technical services related to IT),
- Maintain of IT documentation (application users, preparation of tenders for the purchase of equipment and software, contracts with contractors).

#### Uralsib

Senior IT Specialist декабрь 2009 - май 2010 (6 месяцев) Москва, Россия

- Technical support and solution of problems of internal and external users of the bank in HP OpenView Service Desk.
- Support of legal entities and individuals operating in the BS-client.
- Advised customer support users remote banking services ("e-customer", "Internet Service Bank", "Uralsib +"), support of IT-structures of the bank clients in resolving issues on work with the services of the company.

<sup>&</sup>quot;Tupperware" LLC

System Administrator май 2008 - сентябрь 2009 (1 год 5 месяцев) Москва. Россия

- Administration of domain structure based on Microsoft Server (Windows Server 2003, AD, File Server, DNS, DHCP, GPO etc.) and end-user support (Windows XP Pro, XP Home, Win7, Windows Mobile 6 / 6.1 / 6.5)
- Backup and Data Recovery (Veritas backup),
- Support of internal PBX (Avaya),
- Interaction with contractors (equipment suppliers, mobile operators, service providers, technical services related to IT),
- Maintain IT documentation (application users, equipment purchases, contracts with contractors)
- Introduction of user requests (problems, requests for equipment, IT support activities undertaken by the company, Skype conferences).

"Houston" System administration team Assistant System Administrator / System Administrator октябрь 2006 - апрель 2008 (1 год 7 месяцев) Москва, Россия

- Administration of LAN (Windows Server 2003, AD, DNS, DHCP, configure user groups and security policies)
- Advice and support for end-users (Windows 95, 98, 2000, XP, Vista),
- Installation work on the development and renewal of the network (Ethernet, Wi-Fi),
- Check assembly connecting and configuring newly purchased equipment,
- Installation and update of anti-virus software on machines of end-users and updating anti-virus databases on the server (Symantec, KAV, AVG, Avast),
- Maintenance and inventory of office equipment,
- Maintaining a database of user requests and database for the purchase of new equipment.

## Образование

Тульский Государственный Университет специалист, "Электроснабжение" · (2000 - 2005)

Тульский механический техникум им.С.И.Мосина техник-электрик, "Электроснабжение промышленных предприятий и гражданских сооружений" · (1996 - 2000)